- 好   - 啊
- Okay.     - Aah.
我要搬过去 房租就给你缴了
Listen, I'm gonna be moving out, so you are gonna be in charge of paying the rent.
- 也对 什么时候要缴？ - 1号
- Right, and when is that due?     - First of the month.
每个月吗？
And that's every month?
不是 你想住的月分才要缴
No, just the months you actually want to live here.
啊
Ah.
这是电话费
Okay, here's the phone bill.
噢 我的天
Oh, my God!
那是电话号码
That's our phone number.
是我突然决定要搬走的
Look, I know I kind of sprung this whole me-moving-out-on-you thing.
- 所以我先帮你档一阵子吧   - 不行
- So why don't I just cover you for a while?     - No, no. No way.
乔伊崔比亚尼不接受施舍
Joey Tribbiani does not take charity...
再也不了
anymore.
- 这不是施舍   - 不行 别再说了
- It's not charity, Joe.     - No, forget it.
谢谢 但我不想再拿你的钱了
Okay? I mean, thanks, but I'm done taking money from you.
我可以照顾自己 还有什么？
All right? I can take care of myself. Now, what's next? Come on.
好 这是电费
Okay, uh, here's the electric bill.
- 用个电要这么多钱？ - 对
- This is how much we pay for electric?     - Well, yeah.
其他的帐单待会再看咯？
So we'll do the rest of the bills later, then?
老友记 第六季 第六集
那乔伊得搬出去吗？
So is Joey gonna have to give up the apartment?
希望不用 我想给他钱 但是他不收
I hope not. I tried to offer him money, but he wouldn't take it.
你觉得他需要多少？
How much do you think he needs?
我想1千5应该够他活几个月
I figure $1500 would cover him for a few months, you know...
但我得骗他收下 免得伤害他的自尊
but I have to trick him into taking it so I don't hurt his pride.
你怎么不雇他当演员？
Yeah. Well, why don't you hire him as an actor?
你可以叫他扮装演短剧 怎样都行
You could have him dress up and put on little skits whenever you want.
那样对自尊确实有帮助
Well, that would help the pride thing.
- 嘿   - 嗨
- Hey.     - Hey.
你真是水当当 明天要不要搬来跟我住？
Wow, you look great. Do you wanna move in with me tomorrow?
- 好啊   - 好
- Okay.     - Okay.
你们女生今晚要做什么？
What do you girls have planned for tonight?
与其难过我和瑞秋要分开
Instead of being sad that tonight's my last night with Rachel...
我们觉得不如去吃饭庆祝
we thought we'd go out and celebrate:
瑞秋要搬去跟菲比住
Rachel's moving in with Phoebe.
- 还有我的生日   - 今天不是你的生日
- And also my birthday. Ha, ha.     - It's not your birthday.
这样讲好恶劣
What a mean thing to say.
我就不会戳破你
I would never tell you it was not your birthday.
- 嘿   - 嗨
- Hey.     - Hey.
你们男生有什么节目吗？
Hey, so you guys have anything planned for the big last night?
与其一起打混 我们决定什么也不做
Well, instead of just hanging out, we figure we'd do nothing.
今晚是《尼克队》开慕战
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Knicks' season opener tonight.
我以为你们会想来我家看
I thought maybe you guys would come and watch it.
不知道耶
I don't know, Ross.
我怕你又吹说你放弃打球
Not if you talk about how you gave up basketball...
去当古生物学家
to become a paleontologist.
我本来就放弃打球 去当古生物学家
I did give up a career in basketball to become a paleontologist.
- 菲比 我在想   - 你还没换衣服？
- Pheebs, I was wondering...     - You're not dressed yet?
我们15分钟后就要去玩了
We're supposed to start having fun in 15 minutes!
而且早1分钟都不行
Well, and clearly, not a minute sooner.
你都打包好了吧？拜托你说是
Rachel, you are packed, though, right? I mean, please tell me you're packed.
我当然打包好了 你别紧张
Of course I'm packed. Monica, relax.
我只是想问菲比我该穿什么
I wanted to ask Phoebe for her opinion on what I should wear.
天哪 我真是一刻也不得闲
My God, I cannot get a minute of peace.
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
摩妮卡会宰了你
Monica's just gonna kill you.
我知道
I know.
你穿这样蛮适合惨死的
What you're wearing is fine for that.
瑞秋 我要借
Rachel, I want to borrow
你没打包
You're not packed!
你根本没打包
You're not packed even a little bit.
惊喜
Surprise.
什么？你别发疯 是这样的
Don't get mad, because, look, this is what happened.
我开始打包 然后想到"我在干嘛？"
So I started packing, and then I realized, "What am I doing?"
我最不会打包了 对吧？
I am lousy at packing, right?
但你最爱打包了
But you love packing.
所以做为我的临别赠礼
So as a gift to you on our last night...
哈哈
Ta-da.
我可以当总指挥
I'll be coordinator.
对不起 我没帮你准备礼物
Oh, my God, I'm so sorry. I didn't get you anything.
噢
Oh.
大家都要帮忙 菲比你可以帮忙吧？
Look, everybody has to help. Phoebe, you can help, can't you?
我有事
I have plans.
- 你是跟我们有约   - 没错
- You have plans with us.     - That's right.
钱德可以贴纸箱 罗斯封箱 乔伊搬东西
All right. Chandler can make boxes, Ross can wrap, and Joey can lift things.
- 菲比 去通知男生帮忙   - 好
- Tell the guys they have to help out.     - Okay.
- 好了   - 天呐 谢谢你
- Okay.     - My God, thank you.
快逃 摩妮卡要叫你们收东西 她把工作都分好了
Hurry! Monica's gonna make you pack. She's got jobs for everyone.
我是躲不掉了 你们快逃
Now, it's too late for me, but save yourselves.
好的
Okay.
搬家公司11个小时后会来 瑞秋还没打包
The movers will be here in 11 hours. Rachel has not packed.
每个人都得帮忙 钱德 你先从
Now, everybody has to help. Chandler...
不行 我和乔伊有事
No, I have plans with Joey.
- 你不是说你们没事？ - 这是最后次了嘛
- I thought you said you were doing nothing.     - Yes, but for the last time.
好吧 罗斯
Okay, fine. Now, Ross...
- 我没办法帮忙   - 为什么？
- Oh, but I can't do it.     - Why not?
- 班要来   - 因为班要来
- Don't you have Ben?     - Because I have Ben.
都快8点了 他都快上床了 他在哪里？
It's almost 8:00, it's almost past his bedtime. Where is he?
他去参加晚宴
He's at a dinner party.
他真的要来？我看得见你家喔
Is he really coming? Because I can see into your apartment.
当然是真的
Of course he is. Uh, what?
难道我会拿儿子当借口？
You think I'd just use my son as an excuse?
你以为我是什么样的父亲呢？
What kind of father do you think I am?
好吧 对不起
All right. Sorry.
我得做个班的人偶
I gotta go make a fake Ben.
来了 室友时代最后的彼萨
Here it is. Our last pizzas together as roommates.
我不知道你会买披萨 我叫了中国菜
I wish I'd known you were gonna do that. I ordered Chinese.
没关系
Oh. Oh, that's okay.
其实这样蛮好的
Hey, actually, in a way it's kind of nice. You know?
我们最后的两人晚餐 我带我祖先的食物
Our last dinner together. Me, bringing the food of my ancestors...
你带你祖先的食物
you, the food of yours.
啊？
Huh?
乔伊 我有个比较奇怪的想法
Say, Joe, I had a strange idea for what to do on our last night.
我们来打几盘赌钱如何？
What do you say we play a little, uh, foosball for money?
你疯啦？自97年伤后复出 你就没赢过我
Are you crazy? You haven't beaten me once since my injury- plagued '97 season.
你拿钱送我还比较快
It'd be easier if you'd just give me your money.
是啊
Yes, it would.
你觉得50元如何？
Ahem. What do you say to $50?
- 好 赌了   - 好 开赛
- Okay, you're on.     - Okay, let's play.
世纪之战 意大利队
The big game. Italy versus...
当然是中国队
China, apparently.
看 是直排轮鞋
Oh, look, it's the Rollerblades.
天呐
Oh, God.
记得我们什么时候买的吗？
You remember when we got these?
不记得
No.
那你应该不在
Oh, I guess you weren't there.
喂 我们说过要开心的
You guys, we said we were gonna have fun.
别这样 记不记得那次
Come on. Hey, ha, ha, remember the time?
你们不记得吗？
You don't remember?
对不起 要搬走我真的很难过
Sorry, Pheebs. I guess I'm just really sad that I'm leaving.
我会很想你
I'm gonna miss you so much.
其实不必这么难过
Well, this doesn't have to be so sad though, you know?
别再想你们会想念对方了
Instead of thinking about how much you're gonna miss about each other...
想想你们不会怀念的事
you should, like, think about some of the things you're not gonna miss.
我不认为有什么
I don't think there's anything.
来吧 总会有那么一两件
Come on, there's gotta be something.
没有 她太完美了
Nope. She's perfect.
我有一件
I have one.
很好 你先说
Good. Great. Okay, you can go first.
我不会想念
Uh, well, I guess I'm not gonna miss the fact...
你不准我把留言笔拿走
that you're never allowed to move the phone pen. Ha, ha.
说得好 摩妮卡 你有吗？
That's a good one. Okay, Monica, anything?
瑞秋会把留官笔拿走吗？
You know, does Rachel move the phone pen?
- 有时候会   - 哈 哈
- Aw, sometimes.     - Ha, ha.
其实每次都会
Always, actually.
这就对了 这样不是好多了？
Good. There you go. Doesn't everyone feel better?
不只是留官笔
It's not just the phone pen.
我老是收不到留言
It's just that I never get my messages.
你收到啦
You get your messages.
趁你在沙发上睡着
Well, I don't think it counts if you have to read them off your hand...
去看你的手背应该不算
after you've fallen asleep on the couch.
那你是没接到谁的留言？钱德？
So you missed a message from who? Chandler?
还是你妈？
Or your mom?
还是钱德？
Or Chandler?
还是你妈？
Or your mom?
太好了 成功了 没人难过了
Great, it worked. No one's sad. Heh.
- 太棒了   - 万岁
- Yes.     - Ah.
我又赢了 你已经欠我5百了
I win again. Ha, ha, that's, like, 500 bucks you owe me. Woo- hoo!
5百元
Man. Five hundred dollars.
值很多电
That is a lot of electricity, huh? Woo- hoo!
我得买点吃的
Ooh, I gotta buy some food.
给我捞本的机会 骤死赛
Okay, okay. Give me a chance to win my money back. Sudden death...
一球1千
one goal, $1000.
- 真的？ - 当然
- You serious?     - Oh, yes.
好
Okay.
- 准备欠我钱吧   - 好
- Get ready to owe me.     - Okay.
来吧 好了吗？
Okay, here we go. Ready?
- 不   - 不
- No, no, no!     - No, no, no!
没人能赢我
No one can beat me.
看吧 所以只有小假人 可以出脚
See, now that's why only the little fake men are supposed to do the kicking.
哈啰
Hello?
罗斯 看吧 还有别人会打来
Oh, hi, Ross. See, other people call me.
你老哥 了不起
Ooh, your brother. Score.
- 怎样？ - 我跟班在一起
- What's up?     - I'm here with Ben.
想跟你问个好
Thought we'd say hi.
- 叫他听   - 班 跟摩妮卡姑姑打招呼
- Put him on.     - Ben, say hi to Aunt Monica.
看来他现在不想说话
Oh, I guess he doesn't feel like talking right now.
不过他在笑
Uh, he's smiling, though.
好 待会再聊
Okay, talk to you later.
我觉得你们难过时比较好
I think it was better when you guys were sad.
记得这双直排轮鞋吗？
Hey, oh, remember the Rollerblades? Oh.
你知道我还不会想念什么？"我是摩妮卡
You know what else I'm not gonna miss? "I'm Monica.
我一天刷十七次马桶 有人在上也照刷"
I wash the toilets 17 times a day, even if people are on it."
我是瑞秋 我的毛衣太紧了吗？
"Hi, I'm Rachel. Is my sweater too tight? No?
不会？那我得洗一洗让它缩水
Oh, I'd better wash it and shrink it."
我是摩妮卡 都没有有趣的人留言给我
"I'm Monica. I don't get phone messages from interesting people. Ever."
我会打给她
Hey, I call her.
天哪 我爱罗斯 我恨罗斯 我爱罗斯 我恨罗斯
"Oh, my God. I love Ross. I hate Ross. I love Ross. I hate Ross."
天哪 我交不到男朋友
"Oh, my God. I can't find a boyfriend.
干脆到对面去
So I guess I'll just stumble across the hall
看到谁就上谁
and sleep with the first guy I find in there."
如果想赶去餐厅就得快了
Yeah, we should get a move on if we want to make those dinner reservations.
还是不能玩？
Still broken?
真是烂透了
It sucks, man.
你在这里的最后一晚 我却失去两样最重要的东西
Your last night here, and I lose the two most important things:
手足球桌和
The foosball table...
5百元
and $500.
有别的办法可以把钱赢回去
Well, you know, there are other ways you can win back your money.
- 要不要玩廿一点？ - 我不喜欢玩廿一点
- How about blackjack?     - Ah, not my game.
那就玩 我们可以玩个新游戏
Okay, uh, you know what? We can play a new game.
- 很好玩的一个游戏   - 叫什么名字？
- A new game. It's fun.     - What's it called?
杯牌
Cups.
- 我不会玩杯牌   - 我教你 来嘛 简单又好玩
- I don't know how to play Cups.     - I'll teach you. It's really easy and fun.
- 好吧   - 好 拿牌
- All right.     - Okay, here you go.
我有两张皮蛋 你呢？
I have two queens. What do you have?
- 二和五   - 你赢了50元
- A two and a five.     - Whoa, you win. Fifty dollars.
- 真的？ - 没错 再玩
- Really?     - Oh, yeah. Okay, let's play again. Ready?
- 你是什么牌？ - 四和九
- What have you got?     - A four and a nine.
你开玩笑的吧？
You're kidding, right?
- 怎么了？ - 那是满杯
- No. Why?     - Well, that's a full cup.
我真是杯牌高手
Damn, I am good at Cups.
我不要跟她说话
I'm not talking to her.
总得有人先开口
One of you has to take the first step...
这个人应该是你 因为她要搬走
and it should be you because she's the one who's leaving.
她比较难过
It's harder for her.
也许吧
Maybe you're right.
但她嘲笑我的留言笔
But she made fun of my phone pen.
我知道 我也觉得很过分
I know. I took it hard too.
瑞秋 刚才的事我很
Listen, Rachel, I feel bad about what happened...
- 你在干什么？ - 把东西拿出来
- What are you doing?     - I'm unpacking.
- 什么？ - 我不搬了 这幅画正吗？
- What?     - I'm not moving. Is that picture straight?
离左边差了十万八千里
It needs to go about 20 blocks to the left.
你知道吗？
Hey, you know what?
是你要改变 跟钱德同居
You're the one who wants this big change and move in with Chandler.
你才应该走 为什么要我走？
You should go. Why do I have to leave?
- 因为这是我的房子   - 它也是我的 还有呢？
- Because It's my apartment!     - Well, it's mine too. What else you got?
还有就是你要搬出去
How about: You're moving!
- 不   - 要
- No, no, no.     - Yes, yes, yes.
好了 摩妮卡
Okay, Monica...
这样太可笑了
This is ridiculous.
我们应该帮你打包
We should be packing you.
- 你们谈得怎样？ - 很好 摩妮卡要搬走
- Hey, how you guys doing?     - Great. Monica's moving.
我才没有
I am not!
是吗？那为什么你的东西 都在这徊箱子里？
Oh, really? Well, how come all your stuff is in this box?
好 我知道是怎么回事了
Okay, you guys, you guys, I think I know what's going on here.
喂 停
Okay? You guys? Stop!
你们是假装生气 以免舍不得
I know that you're acting mad because you think that will make it easier to leave.
其实内心深处你们还是很难过
But deep down, you're still really sad. Deep, deep down.
- 不 我很生气   - 最最最深处
- No, Phoebe, I am mad!     - Well, deep, deep, deep down.
我就是很生气
Yeah, I'm just mad.
那就继续追吧
Then keep running.
你赢了
You win.
- 你是什么牌？ - 不重要 什么都比不上
- What did you have?     - Doesn't matter. Nothing beats...
三和六
a three and a six.
那叫D罩杯
That, my friend, is "D Cup."
你目前为止赢了多少？
Okay, now, how much have you won so far?
- 哇7百   - 不是正好7百吧？
- Wow. Seven hundred.     - Not 700 exactly?
- 是啊   - 再加7百
- Yeah.     - Heh. Double it.
- 什么？ - 在杯牌里 一旦赢到7百
- What?     - Yeah, see, in Cups, once you get $700...
就得自动加码
you have to double it.
- 真的？ - 规则又不是我订的
- Really?     - Hey, I didn't make up the rules.
拿到加码奖金后 你可以拿一张牌
Okay, so now, after you receive the doubling bonus, you get, uh, one card.
那张牌有可能值1百元 让你总共赢得1千5
Now, that one card could be worth $100, which brings your total to 1500.
- 噢   - 不
- Ooh.     - No, no, no.
别太兴奋 除非你拿到 不会吧
Don't get too excited, because that's not gonna happen unless you get the... No way.
这是最后一箱衣服
Well, this is the last box of your clothes.
我会在上面注明 "你在想什么？"
I'm just gonna label it "What were you thinking?"
有意思 我正想到对面 在钱德身上那样写
Funny, I was just gonna go across the hall and write that on Chandler.
两位 不是我想雪上加霜
Okay, you guys, I don't mean to make things worse, but...
但我不想跟瑞秋住了
I don't wanna live with Rachel anymore.
- 什么？ - 你们对对方好坏
- What?     - You're just so mean to each other.
我不想跟瑞秋翻脸 我还是喜欢你
And I don't wanna end up like that with Rachel. I still like you.
没关系 因为我不搬了
Well, Phoebe, that's fine because I'm not moving.
菲比 你一定要收留她
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Phoebe, you gotta take her.
我说了很多她的坏话
You know, I know I said some bad stuff...
但瑞秋也有一些好室友的特质
but Rachel does have some qualities that make her a good roommate.
是吗？像什么？
Oh, really? Like what, Monica?
她有几千双靴子
You know how she has 147,000 pair of boots?
真是个好的开始
Oh, yeah, good start, Mon.
- 她会借给你穿   - 是的
- She lets you borrow them.     - Yeah.
然后你再用你的大脚把它撑大
And you stretch them out with your big old clown feet.
你想睡路边吗？天气要变冷罗
Do you wanna live outside? Because it's getting cold.
她有一大堆目录
She gets tons of catalogs...
她会把我会喜欢的部分折起来
and, um, she'll fold down the pages of the things she thinks I'd like.
- 还有呢？ - 唔...
- What else?     - Uh...
我洗澡时
When I take a shower...
她会在镜子上留言给我
she leaves me little notes on the mirror.
那确实是
Yeah, I do. I do do that.
真好 我喜欢浴室里有东西可读
That's nice. I like having things to read in the bathroom.
我在沙发上看书看到睡着
When I fall asleep on the couch after reading...
她会帮我盖毯子
she covers me over with a blanket.
我不希望你冷到
Well, you know, I don't want you to be cold.
当我说我要跟钱德同居时
And when I told her I was gonna be moving in with Chandler...
她非常支持我
she was really supportive.
你真好
You were so great.
让我无后顾之忧
You made it so easy.
现在你要走了
And now you have to leave.
我得跟一个男生住了
And I have to live with a boy!
不会有事的
It's gonna be fine.
瑞秋 我真希望你赶快搬进来
Okay, Rachel. Now I can't wait to live with you.
而且我们应该
You know what we should do?
把摩妮卡也带来
Bring Monica, and then we can all live there together.
一定会很好玩
We'll have so much fun!
但是她要跟钱德住
But, honey, I think she's moving in with Chandler.
也对
Oh, that's right.
你还是要跟他住吗？
You're still set on that?
应该吧
Kind of.
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
喂？摩妮卡
Hello? Hey, Mon.
打包的怎么样了？
How's the packing going?
班？他很好 他就在 妈呀
Ben? He's fine. Yeah, he's right... Oh, my God.
把头从衣服里伸出来
Get your head out of your shirt there, son.
什么？
What?
对 是南瓜 我过去帮忙
Yeah, it's a pumpkin. I'll come pack.
嘿
Hey.
- 怎么了？ - 罗斯和我帮忙打包
- What's wrong?     - Ross and I were helping the girls pack...
在休息时 我跟他玩杯牌输了1千5
took a little break. I lost $1500 to him in Cups.
玩杯牌怎么会输？
Wha...? How did you lose at Cups?
跟你输的方式样
The same way you lost.
我先拿到老K和皮蛋 砰 罗斯拿到2和3
I started out with the king and the queen. Bam. Ross gets a two and a three.
然后我拿到杰克和老K 砰 罗斯拿到4和5
Then I get a jack and a king. Boom. Ross gets a four and five.
罗斯拿到满杯D罩杯
Even Ross was getting the Cup card, the D Cup...
和自动加码 我连半副杯牌都凑不到
the sitting- down bonus. Meanwhile, I didn't even get a half cup. Nothing.
天哪
Oh, man.
他之前也没玩过
He never played before either.
你猜我在想什么 我觉得玩杯牌都靠新手的牌运
You know what I think? I think beginner's luck, very important in Cups.
好 我们再玩一把
Let's just play one more hand. One more hand.
不要 我1毛钱也输不起了 我是说真的
No, no more. I cannot lose another dime. I'm serious this time.
事实上 我要送你一样东西
In fact, look. There's... I wanna give you something, okay?
现在先送 免得我为了赌债拿去当
And let me give it to you now before I pawn it for Cups money.
我要把大白狗送给你
Now, I want you to have the big, white dog...
谢谢你这些年来的照顾
as a... Kind of a thank- you for being such a great roommate.
我不能收 你很喜欢这个雕像
I can't take the big, white dog. You love it.
他不是雕像 他是活的
It's "him." Not "it."
要是我跟你买呢？
Well, what if I bought it from you, you know?
你可以以合理的价格卖给我
And then your nice gesture would be giving it to me at a reasonable price.
1千5如何？
Say $1500?
等一下 我知道你想干嘛了
Wait a second. I see what you're trying to do here.
你又想塞钱给我
You're trying to give me money again.
我什么时候塞钱给你了？
When did I try to give you money?
之前看帐单的时候
Before, over there with the bills.
你想施舍我 我说不要 你也就算了
You tried to give me charity, I said no, you dropped it.
然后我们开心度过最后一晚
Okay, then we had a nice last night together.
说笑 赌钱 谁也没塞钱给谁
We had some fun, we gambled, nobody tried to give anybody any money.
现在你突然又想来这套
Now, out of the blue, you start with the charity thing again.
我只是想帮助你 我想确定你的生活没问题
I'm just trying to help you out, okay? I wanna make sure that you're okay.
我会没问题的 你听着
I will be okay. Look, Chandler.
你不能老觉得我无法照顾自己
You gotta get it out of your head that I can't take care of myself, okay?
我不会怀念你借钱给我
Look, I'm not gonna miss you helping me out with money.
我唯一会怀念的
The only thing I'm gonna miss...
就是你
is you.
现在还有这只狗
And now the dog.
嘿
Hey.
- 到了打电话给我 好吗？ - 好
- Call me when you get there, okay?     - Okay.
我真的会很想你
I'm really gonna miss you.
钥匙要还你
Oh, I have your key.
- 拿去   - 谢谢
- Here you go.     - Thanks.
天哪 多好笑 再过几小时就会见面了
Oh, God, this is silly. I'm gonna see you in a couple of hours.
房子再见
Bye, house.
- 再见   - 再见
- Bye- bye.     - Bye.
嘿
Hey.
- 她真的走了   - 我知道
- She really left.     - I know.
- 谢谢你   - 不客气 室友
- Thank you.     - No problem, roomie.
- 我可以问你个问题吗？ - 当然可以
- Can I ask you a question?     - Sure.
那只狗怎么会在这里？
What the hell is that dog doing here?
我捏造了杯牌好塞钱给乔伊
I invented the game of Cups as a way to give Joey money.
- 现在你想把钱要回去   - 没错
- And now you want that money back?     - Exactly.
钱德 你以为我是白痴吗？
Chandler, what kind of idiot do you take me for?
没有那种牌 那是我捏造的
It's not a real game. I made it up.
很遗憾你输钱 但我赢得光明正大
I'm sorry you lost your money. But I won it fair and square.
游戏是假的
At a fake game!
如果你想赢一点回去
Now, if you wanna try to make some of it back...
我愿意陪你玩 但我必须警告你
I'd be glad to play you for it. But I should warn you.
我是杯牌高手
I am very good at Cups.
好 你上次玩 有出现杯盘牌吧？
Okay, now, I assume the saucer card came up when you played last?
- 没有   - 嗯
- No.     - Hmm.
看看这次会不会出现
Let's see if it comes up this time.